aerogardenstore.com 2017-12-05

# Privacy Policy

**AeroGrow North American Information Privacy & Security Policy**

AeroGrow is committed and accountable to comply with the AeroGrow Global Information Privacy & Security Policy and applicable law, including the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA), to maintain the privacy of your personal information collected at this website. We encourage you to read this privacy statement carefully. 

The Information We Collect   
AeroGrow may collect the following types of information from you at this website or through the AeroGarden App: 

Transaction Information   
If you enter into a transaction (such as a purchase) at this website, you will be required to provide information that is needed to complete the transaction, including your name, billing and shipping address, product selection(s), and your payment information. We do not store any credit/debit card information, only encrypted "tokens" for security purposes.

Automatically Collected Information   
We passively collect information that is automatically sent to us by your web browser while visiting our site. This information typically includes generic, non personally identifiable information like timestamp, urls, and IP address. The amount of information sent by your web browser depends on its settings. We use this information to develop statistics that help us understand how our visitors use our website and to improve the visitor experience. 

Cookie Generated Information   
When you visit our site, we install a marker on your computer commonly called a "cookie." By providing you with a unique cookie, we are able to create a database of your previous choices and preferences, and in situations where these choices or preferences need to be collected again; they can be supplied by us automatically, saving you time and effort. Your computer may be specially configured to reject cookies; please refer to your browser settings for more information. AeroGrow websites will allow you to visit without accepting cookies, but some features of our websites will not work properly if you choose to reject cookies. 

User Generated Information   
We collect information at this website when you contact us or respond to the surveys, questionnaires or applications we make available. If you e-mail us, you are voluntarily releasing the content of your e-mail to us (including your e-mail address). If you enter information or answer questions we have placed on the website, you are also voluntarily releasing that information to us. 

User Reviews  
We have made arrangements with PowerReviews, Inc. (d/b/a Buzzillions) ("PowerReviews") to facilitate the collection of consumer product reviews of products sold by AeroGrow International, Inc. When you submit a product review to AeroGrow.com, you are also subject to PowerReviews’ terms of use and privacy policies. Accordingly, you should review those policies prior to submitting a review. Also, reviews you submit may be posted on both www.Buzzillions.com and our web sites. 

How Information is Collected, Used and Disclosed   
AeroGrow may use any of the information gathered at this website (other than credit information) for any legal purpose. We may analyze personal information for historical, statistical or scientific purposes, or we may store the personal information using cookies for your convenience should you return to this website in the future. 

We may also use your personal information to investigate security breaches or cooperate with government authorities pursuant to a legal matter. Personal information collected online may also be combined with information you have provided to AeroGrow through other sources such as product registrations, call centers, or publicly such as at trade shows or seminars. 

In addition, we may have collected similar information from you in the past, before our Global Information Privacy & Security Policy took effect. By using this website you agree to the terms of this privacy statement. We obtain your consent to collect, use, or disclose you personal information by a method that is appropriate to the type of personal information being collected, used, or disclosed. By agreeing to the terms of this privacy statement you are consenting to our continued use of previously collected information under the terms of this privacy statement. 

Direct Marketing   
AeroGrow may use all information collected at this website for direct marketing purposes including the sharing of the information with pre-determined third parties who are bound by agreements with AeroGrow to secure and protect the confidentiality of your personal information, unless you specifically request that it not be used for that purpose by emailing customerservice@aerogrow.com. 

Links to Other Sites   
For your convenience, this page may contain certain hyperlinks to other AeroGrow websites as well as to third party non-AeroGrow sites. While AeroGrow websites are subject to this privacy statement, we can make no promises or guarantees regarding data collection on the hyperlinked pages and sites that are not owned by AeroGrow. We therefore recommend that you read the privacy statement for each third party site you visit. 

Children's Information   
AeroGrow is committed to protecting the privacy needs of children, and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities. AeroGrow does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13, and AeroGrow does not target its websites to children under 13. If we determine that an individual under the age of 13 has submitted information to an AeroGrow website, we will delete that information. 

Information Security   
AeroGrow uses commercially reasonable methods consistent with industry practice to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure appropriate use of your personal information. AeroGrow keeps your personal information up to date, accurate, and relevant for its intended use. 

Corrections and to Opt Out   
AeroGrow responds in a timely manner to your questions, concerns, and complaints about the privacy of your personal information and our privacy and security policy and procedures. If you do not want us to use your personal information as described in this statement or if you wish to request access to your personal information we have on record in order to review and correct the information, please contact us by phone at 800-476-9669, by email at customerservice@aerogrow.com or by mail at PO Box 18450, Boulder, CO, USA 80308-1450. 

Our company and our trusted third parties may collect and share anonymous versions of user information. We may use that information to link to and issue an anonymous cookie containing demographic or intent-based data for online behavioral advertising. Such cookies do not contain personally identifiable information. If you would like to opt out of online behavioral advertising, click on one of the links below. (<http://www.aboutads.info/choices> or <http://networkadvertising.org/choices>) 

*PIPEDA: the following principles to govern the collection, use and disclosure of personal information: accountability, identifying the purposes for the collection of personal information, obtaining consent, limiting collection, limiting use, disclosure and retention, ensuring accuracy, providing adequate security, making information management policies readily available, providing individuals with access to information about themselves, and giving individuals a right to challenge an organization's compliance with these principles.
